Day 14
I'm going a little bit out front.
Man,
excuse me brother.
Can I fuck?
Seriously,
how are you?
Fell pleasure.
Sometimes when we start listening to everyone,
we don't listen to ourselves.
You know you have to believe a little more in my idea that I came here to do,
which is to set up a business.
If what I'm planning on works out today,
the game will change.
I'm always watching.
In addition to selling,
you know the entrepreneur has to start looking at other opportunities.
And then I was thinking about it.
You know man,
how can I be more creative about connecting
with people being me and my signature,
right?
Man,
I think I'm going to invest in the best idea to turn this series around,
now man,
let's have faith that it will work.
Today I will invest in my business.
A guy is waiting for me and I'm going there to see if I can close the deal.
Closed bro action bro we're together.
Thank God,
thank you.
Ah.